The SCOAN Sunday Service
As Jesus was leaving the city of Jericho
There was blind Bartimaeus begging beside the road
When he heard it was Jesus coming close
Ignoring the opposing crowd
He cried out with a loud voice saying
Son of David have mercy on me
Let Your mercy speak for me
Your Divine favour locate me
Son of David have mercy on me
As Jesus was leaving the city of Jericho
There was blind Bartimaeus begging beside the road
When he heard it was Jesus coming close
Ignoring the opposing crowd
He cried out with a loud voice saying
Son of David have mercy on me
Let Your mercy speak for me
Your Divine favour locate me
Son of David have mercy on me
Let Your mercy speak for me
Your Divine favour locate me
Son of David have mercy on me
Can you hear that? The blind Bartimaeus had been begging for money,
but money could not solve his problem.
He had been begging for alms but that couldn't solve his problem.
When he heard that Jesus of Nazareth was coming close - do you know that desperation has a sound?
Desperation has a sound.
He cried out! He cried!
He said, "Son of David! Son of David!! Son of David, have mercy on me!
Have mercy!"
He cried, "Let your mercy speak for me".
He said, "Your Divine favour, Lord, come onto me.
Help me!"
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Jesus!
Lift your voice!
Son of David have mercy on me
He shouted, "Son of David, help me!"
Let Your mercy speak for me
Your Divine favour locate me
Son of David have mercy on me
I want you to make a desperation sound, cry out, "Son of David!"
Desperation has a sound.
Make that sound for your children at home, husband, wife, career - desperation has a sound.
He did not allow the opposing crowd to hold him down.
Right now, forget about yourself - make a sound.
Heaven wants to hear you; the Son of David wants to hear you.
Make a sound!
Make that sound for your children, husband, wife, career - desperation has a sound.
Lord, don't leave me alone; Lord, don't forsake me!
Help me! I need You!
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Make that sound! Cry out!
With your heart, cry out! Son of David, have mercy on me, don't leave me!
Lord, save me, don't let go!
Son of David, have mercy on me!
Don't leave me!
I need You! I need Your strength, favour, and mercy!
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Make it louder!
Son of David! Jesus Christ of Nazareth, don't leave me!
I will never let You go, unless You bless me!
I will never let You go, unless You deliver me!
I will never let You go, unless You heal me!
I will never let You go! No!
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Have mercy on me
Thank You, Jesus! Thank You, Lord!
Give Him thanks!
Say, thank You, Lord! Thank You for Your mercy!
Thank You for Your favour! Thank You, Lord!